Guide to the Gay Cable Network Archives, 1982-2001 MSS.231
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XXI: Political Conventions, 155948
  - Conventions '88, Atlanta Democratic National Convention No. 1, July 18, 1988; ID: 231.1400A; 160456 (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1400A)
    Program content: Day One, Demonstrations
  - Conventions '88, Kathleen-A.M. No. 1, July 19, 1988; ID: 231.1401A; 160457 (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1401A)
    Program content: Gay press conference, Karen Clark, Perry [Atkins], Dale McCormick, gay discrimination
  - Conventions '88, Kathleen-A.M. No. 3, July 19, 1988; ID: 231.1402A; 160458 (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1402A)
    Program content: Vic Basile cont., 1 guest, Eleanor Smeal-former pres. NOW, establishing shot, important gay caucus to nominate v. pres., interviews after P. Watkins nominated for vice-pres., Pat Worman, F. Butner
  - Conventions '88, Kathleen-On the Floor P.M. No. 5, July 19, 1988; ID: 231.1403A; 160459 (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1403A)
    Program content: Albert Gore, several good interviews, Mondale, AIDS
  - Conventions '88, Harry No. 1, August 13, 1988; ID: 231.1404A; 160460 (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1404A)
    Program content: AIDS Candlelight, Armstrong Park
  - Conventions '88, Harry No. 2, August 13, 1988; ID: 231.1405A; 160461 (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1405A)
    Program content: AIDS Candlelight
  - Conventions '88, Harry No. 3, August 13, 1988; ID: 231.1406A; 160462 (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1406A)
  - Conventions '88, Harry No. 4, August 13, 1988; ID: 231.1407A; 160463 (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1407A)
  - Conventions '88, Harry No. 5, August 13, 1988; ID: 231.1408A; 160464 (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1408A)
    Program content: Bourbon St.
  - Conventions '88, Allen/Negron NOW Rally, No. 1, August 14, 1988; ID: 231.1409A; 160465 (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1409A)
  - Conventions '88, Armstrong Park Care Fest, August 14, 1988; ID: 231.1410A; 160466 (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1410A)
    Program content: Camera-Parker, Corres. O/Allen
  - Conventions '88, ACT UP Arrestees from Country Club No. 1, August 14, 1988; ID: 231.1411A; 160467 (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1411A)
  - Conventions '88, Harry No. 1, August 14, 1988; ID: 231.1412A; 160468 (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1412A)
    Program content: Rally at Kiss-in St. Louis Cathedral
  - Conventions '88, Young Republicans No. 2, August 14, 1988; ID: 231.1413A; 160469 (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1413A)
    Program content: Camera-Parker, Corres. O. Negron, NOW Rally
  - Conventions '88, ACT UP Reagan, August 14, 1988; ID: 231.1414A; 160470 (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1414A)
    Program content: New Orleans Convention Center, ACT-UP protest of Reagan speech, Footage of outside and inside protests, Interview with Adam Hassuk of ACT-UP describing what happened inside, Chyron-"Courtesy of Testing the Limits"
  - Conventions '88, Gay Republican Party No. 1, August 15, 1988; ID: 231.1415A; 160471 (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1415A)
    Program content: At the mint
  - Conventions '88, Gay Republican Party No. 2, August 15, 1988; ID: 231.1416A; 160472 (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1416A)
  - Conventions '88, Allen AIDS delegates, August 15, 1988; ID: 231.1417A; 160473 (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1417A)
    Program content: Camera-Parker, PA-Tad
  - Conventions '88, Steve-Floor Crew 1 No. 1, August 15, 1988; ID: 231.1418A; 160474 (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1418A)
    Program content: Family, (Ed and Olivia), Gay Vote
  - Conventions '88, Steve-Floor Crew 1 No. 2, August 15, 1988; ID: 231.1419A; 160475 (Box 92, Media ID: 231.1419A)
    Program content: Ed-O, Camera-Steve, N/G
  - Conventions '88, Harry-Floor Crew 2 No. 1, August 15, 1988; ID: 231.1420A; 160476 (Box 92, Media ID: 231.1420A)
    Program content: (Andy and Allen), Family, Vote
  - Conventions '88, Harry-Floor Crew 2 No. 2, August 15, 1988; ID: 231.1421A; 160477 (Box 92, Media ID: 231.1421A)
    Program content: (Andy and Allen), Family Issues, Reagan reaction, 10:40 No civil rights
  - Conventions '88, Harry-Floor Crew 2 No. 3, August 15, 1988; ID: 231.1422A; 160478 (Box 92, Media ID: 231.1422A)
    Program content: End Mom's demonstration, Intro/outro demo, Rep. reactions, Gay Vote
  - Conventions '88, Harry-Floor Crew 2 No. 4, August 15, 1988; ID: 231.1423A; 160479 (Box 92, Media ID: 231.1423A)
    Program content: Wrap ups/intros, Mon. Show
  - Conventions '88, Harry-Mothers No. 2, August 15, 1988; ID: 231.1424A; 160480 (Box 92, Media ID: 231.1424A)
  - Conventions '88, Harry-Die-in A.M. No. 1, August 15, 1988; ID: 231.1425A; 160481 (Box 92, Media ID: 231.1425A)
  - Conventions '88, Republican National Convention No. 1, August 15, 1988; ID: 231.1426; 160482 (Box 92, Media ID: 231.1426)
    TRT: 00:60:00
    Program content: Day 1, Satellite program, No. 5 CGN AIDS gate demonstrations 000
  - Conventions '88, [Container]--Harry-Floor No. 1 [Cassette]--Steve-Floor Crew 2; 8/16/1988, August 16, 1988; ID: 231.1427A; 160484 (Box 92, Media ID: 231.1427A)
    Program content: [Container]--O/ED, Shirley Temple, Maureen Reagan [Cassette]--VP, Fund, Violent, Dole
  - Conventions '88, No. 2, August 16, 1988; ID: 231.1428A; 160485 (Box 92, Media ID: 231.1428A)
    Program content: Carriage Driver controversy, Violence
  - Conventions '88, Harry-Floor No. 2, August 16, 1988; ID: 231.1429A; 160488 (Box 92, Media ID: 231.1429A)
    Program content: O/ED
  - Conventions '88, Harry No. 3, August 16, 1988; ID: 231.1430A; 160489 (Box 92, Media ID: 231.1430A)
    Program content: Commentary Wrap-up and Intros. on floor 3pm, Wrap-ups/Intros. for Tues.
  - Conventions '88, Steve-Crew 2 Floor P.M. No. 2, August 16, 1988; ID: 231.1431A; 160490 (Box 92, Media ID: 231.1431A)
    Program content: VP-Fund, violence, Gay Vote 3, Discrimination 3
  - Conventions '88, Steve-Floor P.M. No. 3, August 16, 1988; ID: 231.1432A; 160491 (Box 92, Media ID: 231.1432A)
    Program content: Fundy-VP, violence, Gay Vote 3
  - Conventions '88, Voice Center No. 1, August 16, 1988; ID: 231.1433A; 160501 (Box 92, Media ID: 231.1433A)
    Program content: Steve/Andy/Tad, Violence, ACT-UP on way to Bush, Urvashi Vaid, Gay Vote, Discrimination
  - Conventions '88, Voice Center Noon No. 2, August 16, 1988; ID: 231.1434A; 160502 (Box 92, Media ID: 231.1434A)
    Program content: Crew No. 2, Steve-Tad-Andy, Violence, Gay Reps., Robert Bray, John Thomas, Gay viewpoint
  - Conventions '88, Republican National Convention No. 2, August 16, 1988; ID: 231.1435A; 160503 (Box 92, Media ID: 231.1435A)
    Program content: Day 2, Traffic No. 2304, Family Issues
  - Conventions '88, Opening with commentator-convention floor, August 17, 1988; ID: 231.1436; 160504 (Box 92, Media ID: 231.1436)
  - Conventions '88, Steve-Floor Eve. No. 1, August 17, 1988; ID: 231.1437A; 160505 (Box 92, Media ID: 231.1437A)
    Program content: Press-Ann McDaniels Newsweek, Bush interview, discrimination
  - Conventions '88, Steve-Floor No. 2, August 17, 1988; ID: 231.1438A; 160506 (Box 92, Media ID: 231.1438A)
    Program content: discrimination, Gay Vote
  - Conventions '88, Steve-Floor No. 4, August 17, 1988; ID: 231.1439A; 160507 (Box 93, Media ID: 231.1439A)
    Program content: Discrimination
  - Conventions '88, Steve-Voice '88 A.M. No. 1, August 17, 1988; ID: 231.1440A; 160508 (Box 93, Media ID: 231.1440A)
    Program content: Gay Vote 1, Press Conference-VP, Violence, AIDS
  - Conventions '88, Steve-Gay Voice '88 A.M. No. 2, [Container]--August 17,1988 [Cassette]--August 18, 1988, August 17 or 18, 1988; ID: 231.1441A; 160509 (Box 93, Media ID: 231.1441A)
    Program content: Gay Vote 1, VP, Violence, Discrimination
  - Conventions '88, Republican National Convention New Orleans No. 3, August 17, 1988; ID: 231.1442A; 160510 (Box 93, Media ID: 231.1442A)
    Program content: Day 3, Violence
  - Conventions '88, N[ew] O[rleans] AIDS Task Force Resource Center, August 18, 1988; ID: 231.1443A; 160511 (Box 93, Media ID: 231.1443A)
    Program content: Harry-O-Parke
  - Conventions '88, Steve-Floor P.M. No. 1, August 18, 1988; ID: 231.1444; 160512 (Box 93, Media ID: 231.1444)
    Program content: Bush/Quail chant.
  - Conventions '88, Steve-Floor P.M. No. 2, August 18, 1988; ID: 231.1445A; 160513 (Box 93, Media ID: 231.1445A)
  - Conventions '88, Steve-Floor P.M. No. 3, August 18, 1988; ID: 231.1446A; 160514 (Box 93, Media ID: 231.1446A)
  - Conventions '88, Wrap-Ups 3pm, August 18, 1988; ID: 231.1447A; 160533 (Box 93, Media ID: 231.1447A)
  - Conventions '88, Republican National Convention New Orleans, August 18, 1988; ID: 231.1448A; 160534 (Box 93, Media ID: 231.1448A)
    Program content: Day 4, Kissenger, Civil Rights and Discrimination
  - Conventions '88, ACT UP Demo Protest No. 1, August 17, 1988; ID: 231.1449A; 160537 (Box 93, Media ID: 231.1449A)
    Program content: Rollerena, Leslie Cagan, Sen. Alan [Cranston]
  - Conventions '88, ACT-UP Demo Protest No. 2, August 17, 1988; ID: 231.1450A; 160538 (Box 93, Media ID: 231.1450A)
    Program content: Morris Knight, Ted Weiss Speech
  - Conventions '88, ACT-UP Demo Protest No. 3, August 17, 1988; ID: 231.1451A; 160539 (Box 93, Media ID: 231.1451A)
    Program content: Lee Harrington
  - Conventions '88, Lesbian Party, August 17, 1988; ID: 231.1452A; 160540 (Box 93, Media ID: 231.1452A)
    Program content: Party interviews with congresswomen, good material, Parade Old South style, party for John Lewis Congr., gay folks in neighborhood, should be good shots
  - Conventions '88, Kathleen-On the Floor P.M. No. 1, August 18, 1988; ID: 231.1453A; 160541 (Box 93, Media ID: 231.1453A)
    Program content: Discrimination, Rep. Henry Waxman-AIDS, Molly Yard, Bill Lynch, Terje Anderson
  - Conventions '88, Kathleen-Caucus No. 3, August 18, 1988; ID: 231.1454A; 160544 (Box 93, Media ID: 231.1454A)
    Program content: Elaine Noble-Family Issues, Andy-discrimination, Vivian-health care transition, general caucus, Andy-stand up intro to Family
  - Conventions '88, Harry-Convention Floor AIDS Testimonies, August 19, 1988; ID: 231.1455A; 160545 (Box 93, Media ID: 231.1455A)
  - Conventions '88, Phil/Kate-Gay Caucus No. 1, August 20, 1988; ID: 231.1456A; 160546 (Box 93, Media ID: 231.1456A)
    Program content: Press Conference with Young, Kiss-in description, Robert Bray, Al Gore and AIDS
  - Conventions '88, Phil/Kate-Gay Caucus No. 2, August 20, 1988; ID: 231.1457A; 160553 (Box 93, Media ID: 231.1457A)
    Program content: Perry Watkins, Robert Bray, Randy Miller, at Hilton
  - Conventions '88, Kathleen No. 1, August 20, 1988; ID: 231.1458A; 160554 (Box 93, Media ID: 231.1458A)
    Program content: Interviews PWA, Quilt confrontation with Police Bystanders, Press Conference and ift on Vice President, more
  - Conventions '88, Phil-Gay Caucus No. 1, August 21, 1988; 2013; 231.1459; 160555 (Box 94, Cassette 231.1459, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1459)
    Brad [Truax]
  - Conventions '88, [1]--Gay Caucus No. 2 [2]--Kathleen-Floor Crew 2 No. 2, August 21, 1988; 231.1460A; 160556 (Box 94, Cassette 231.1460A, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1460A)
  - Conventions '88, Phil/Kate-Gay Caucus No. 3, August 21, 1988; 231.1461; 160557 (Box 94, Cassette 231.1461, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1461)
    1st part-Matilda Keon
  - [1]--C-SPAN Demo Convention Coverage No. 2 [2]--Carter, August 21, 1988; 231.1462; 160558 (Box 94, Cassette 231.1462, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1462)
  - C-SPAN Rep. Convention Night Coverage [Container]--No. 2, August 15, 1988 [Cassette]--No. 1, August 16, 1988, August 15 or 16, 1988; 231.1463; 160559 (Box 94, Cassette 231.1463)
  - Conventions '88, Olivia/Harry-Rally at Lafayette Park 5 P.M., August 17, 1988; 231.1464A; 160560 (Box 94, Cassette 231.1464A, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1464A)
  - Conventions '88, Gay Voice '88 Press Conference No. 1, August 18, 1988; 231.1465A; 160561 (Box 94, Cassette 231.1465A, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1465A)
  - Conventions '88, Republican Convention New Orleans, August 18, 1988; 231.1466A; 160562 (Box 94, Cassette 231.1466A, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1466A)
    Format: S-VHS
  - Conventions '88, Republican Convention New Orleans, August 18, 1988; 231.1467; 160563 (Box 94, Cassette 231.1467, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1467)
    Human Billboard at Security Entrance during last night of convention
  - Elections 1988, 231.1468; 160564 (Box 94, Cassette 231.1468, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1468)
  - Elections, Undated; 231.1469; 160565 (Box 94, Cassette 231.1469, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1469)
    1. Atlanta Interview with Mike Fesco, 2. 5 [guides] Dusty Weather Reports, George Preanius-Celmn., Ex-Houston Mayor Louie Welch shoot in Louie, Mayor Kathy Whitmire-Whitmire Hdqtrs.
  - [Container]--Democratic Convention [Cassette]--Cable Channel 16-"The Library", Undated; 231.1470; 160566 (Box 94, Cassette 231.1470, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1470)
  - Group No. 3-Gay Democratic Club No. 1, Undated; 231.1471A; 160567 (Box 94, Cassette 231.1471A, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1471A)
  - Group No. 3-Gay Democratic Club No. 2, Undated; 2013; 231.1472A; 160568 (Box 94, Cassette 231.1472A, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1472A)
  - [1]--Phyllis Diller Concert-Dallas, August 1984 [2]--Pamela Stanley Texas Freedom Concert-Dallas August 1984 [3]--Frankie Goes to Hollywood-Uncensored [4]--One Man in Search of Love [4]--Frankie Goes to Hollywood-Censored, circa 1984; 231.1473; 160569 (Box 94, Cassette 231.1473, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records 231.1473)
  - [Container]--[1]--National Gay/Lesbian Delegate Conference SF No. 2, 7/13/[1984] [2]--Sister Boom Boom [Cassette]--The Nellie Olsens, circa 1984; ID: 231.1616; 161189 (Box 102, Media ID: 231.1616)
  - Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 25, Convention H, Sixth Day, ID: 231.1617; 161190 (Box 102, Media ID: 231.1617)
    Program content: Ferrara acceptance speech
  - Trip to Atlanta, July 1988; ID: 231.1618; 161191 (Box 102, Media ID: 231.1618)
    Currently not available for viewing..
  - Conventions '88, Kate/Steve/Phil Floor Tape No. 1, August 19, 1988; ID: 231.1619A; 161192 (Box 102, Media ID: 231.1619A)
    Program content: AIDS, Lomay-Atl.
  - Conventions '88, Harry No. 3, August 19, 1988; ID: 231.1620A; 161193 (Box 102, Media ID: 231.1620A)
    Program content: Mayor's Representative in Response to ACT-UP, Interviews-Jesse Fields -Becky Braizer, ACT-UP Leaders
  - Conventions '88, IMREG Demo, August 16, 1988; ID: 231.1621A; 161204 (Box 102, Media ID: 231.1621A)
    Program content: Olivia-correspondent, Hari-camera, Parker-PA
  - Conventions '88, Floor Steve-Tad Tape No. 3, August 16, 1988; ID: 231.1622; 161205 (Box 102, Media ID: 231.1622)
    Program content: Bush Arrival, ACT-UP
  - Conventions '88, ACT UP at Bush Address, Riverwalk New Orleans, 1988; ID: 231.1623; 161206 (Box 102, Media ID: 231.1623)
  - Sound Bites for '88 Conventions, 1988; ID: 231.1624; 161207 (Box 102, Media ID: 231.1624)
    Program content: 1. Family Issues, 2. Civil Rights, 3. Violence and Discrimination
  - Elections 1988, ID: 231.1625; 161208 (Box 102, Media ID: 231.1625)
  - Welcome to the 2000 Republican National Convention, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, ID: 231.1626; 161209 (Box 102, Media ID: 231.1626)
  - Group 3, Vietnam Veterans Memorial and Some Democratic Clubs, Undated; ID: 231.1627; 161210 (Box 102, Media ID: 231.1627)
    Program content: One Veteran at end of tape
  - Rep. Bob Dornan (R-CA)-Republican Presidential Hopeful, Andy Humm, Undated; ID: 231.1628; 161211 (Box 102, Media ID: 231.1628)
  - Pat Buchanan-Republican Presidential Hopeful, Christian Coalition Convention, Andy Humm, Undated; ID: 231.1629; 161212 (Box 102, Media ID: 231.1629)
- Series XXII: Pride and Progress / The Right Stuff, 1985-1990; 154235
  - 1984, 246556
    - [1]--Pride and Progress. Episode No. 1 [2]--The Right Stuff, Episode No. 118 [Air Date: 10/4/1984], October 1984; ID: 231.0599; 155964 (Box 39, Media ID: 231.0599)
      Duration: 01:00:00
      Pride and Progress
      News - highlights:
      1. Massachusetts Congressman Gary Studds, openly gay, wins primary victory; Interview with David Bender of the Studds campaign
      COMMERCIAL: "Badlands," NYC gay bar
      2. Sports report
      3. Federal government requests AIDS funding
      4. Rutgers University offers "Homosexuality in Society" course
      5. FBI files on gay organizations released
      6. Referendum to repeal gay rights in Maryland
      7. Human Rights Commission: gay and lesbian discrimination documentation project; interview with Katy Taylor
      COMMERCIAL: Chamberlain and Associates, career service professionals
      COMMERCIAL: "New York Native"
      8. Three teens charged in death of Charles Howard, a gay man in Maine
      9. Interview with Vivian Shapiro, Human Rights Campaign
      COMMERCIAL: "The Connect"
      Healthline: Conversations with GMHC: Dr. Steven Caiazza discusses "How to Reduce Risk of Getting AIDS"
      COMMERCIAL: World of Video
      The Right Stuff:
      COMMERCIAL: National Fund for Human Dignity with Abigail "Dear Abby" Van Buren
      COMMERCIAL: Pensione, San Francisco Hotel
      1. Interview with Phyllis Diller, entertainer
      COMMERCIAL: H. Clay Friedrichs Realtors, New Jersey
      COMMERCIAL: Rio Adventure, Orpheo travel agency
      2."Brothers," a Showtime cable comedy series
      COMMERCIAL: "People in Touch," a gay dating service
      3. "Fever of an Unknown Origin" - Interviews with actor playwright Stephen Holt, actor Raymie Priesmeyer, scenes from the play
      COMMERCIAL: Spur Productions
      4. Phyllis Diller interview/ closing credits
      COMMERCIAL National Fund for Human Dignity with Judge Steven Lax
    - [1]--Pride and Progress, Episode No. 2 [2]--The Right Stuff, Episode No. 119 [Air Date: 10/5/1984], October 1984; ID: 231.0601; 155966 (Box 39, Media ID: 231.0601)
      Original Format: 3/4 in. Umatic
    - [1]--Pride and Progress, Episode No. 3 [2]--The Right Stuff, Episode No. 120 [Air Date: 10/13/1984], October 1984; ID: 231.0602; 155967 (Box 39, Media ID: 231.0602)
      1. Sentencing of Maine teens in death of Charles Howard, a gay man
      2. San Francisco rejects extending employment benefits to gay partners of city workers
      3. First Ronald Reagan versus Walter Mondale debate viewed by gay Mondale supporters
      4. Sports Report
      5. Interview with Ivan [Deeds] about Gay Narcotics Anonymous
      6. Sweden as a place for political asylum for gays
      7. Sentencing of Gary Lee Hopper, a male hustler, in slashing and attempted robbery of gay man
      8. Gay center opens in Allentown, Pennsylvania
      9. Interview with Peter Vogel, Chairperson for New York Gay Task Force
      10. Interview with Peter Guardino, Gay Police Officers Action League
      11. Proposal to make West Hollywood a city
      Healthline: Conversations with GMHC: Dr. Scott Croxson, Fellow Immunopathology, discusses HTLV virus
      COMMERCIAL: "The Connection," a gay newspaper The Right Stuff:
      COMMERCIAL: National Fund for Human Dignity with actor Mike Farrell
      1. Footage from San Francisco memorial for John Simms, who passed away from AIDS
      2.Interview with director Robert Epstein, producer Richard Schmiechen, and publicist Vito Russo, "The Times of Harvey Milk"
      3. "Swan in Love," commentary and clips about motion picture
      COMMERCIAL National Fund for Human Dignity with actor Jack Albertson
      4. More from interviews about "The Times of Harvey Milk"/ closing credits
    - [1]--Pride and Progress, Episode No. 4 [2]--The Right Stuff, Episode No. 121 [Air Date: 10/22/1984], October 1984; ID: 231.0603; 155968 (Box 39, Media ID: 231.0603)
    - [1]--Pride and Progress, Episode No. 5 [2]--The Right Stuff, Episode No. 122 [Air Date: 10/24/1984], October 1984; ID: 231.0604; 155969 (Box 39, Media ID: 231.0604)
    - [1]--Pride and Progress, Episode No. 6 [2]--The Right Stuff, Episode No. 123 [Air Date: 11/6/1984], November 1984; ID: 231.0605; 155970 (Box 39, Media ID: 231.0605)
      1. New York Executive Order #50 - a non-discrimination policy on city contactors
      2. Interview with Willy Smith, Gay and Lesbian Inter-Religious Coalition
      COMMERCIAL: "New York Native," with Quentin Crisp
      3. Interview with Nancy Roth, executive director of Gay Rights National Lobby, Washington D.C.
      COMMERCIAL: Chamberlain and Associates, Career Service Professionals
      4. AIDS fears in court
      5. Interview with Tim Sweeney, director of LAMBDA Legal Defense, discussing LAMBDA's AIDS Legal Guide
      COMMERCIAL: "Rome Adventure," Orpheo Travel Agency
      6. Interview with Reverend Karen Zeigler, director of Metropolitan Community Church, discussing their on-going application to the National Council of Churches
      COMMERCIAL: "The Times of Harvey Milk"
      7. Gay and lesbian child custody announcement
      8. LAMBDA Democrats, authors night
      COMMERCIAL: Arcos Blancos Resort, San Juan, Puerto Rico
      9. Heathline: Conversations with GMHC: Dr. Jeffrey Lawrence, NY Hospital, Cornell Medical Center, discusses new directions in treating AIDS
      10. Sports Report: Interview with Jim Link and Leslie Randolph, Rambler Soccer Club The Right Stuff:
      1. 1984 Halloween on Christopher Street, NYC
      COMMERCIAL: "The Connection," gay/lesbian newspaper
      2. Lo Nardo, music group, performing
      3. Broadway star Vivian Blaine performing "live" at SAGE Benefit at the Limelight, NYC. Songs: "Guys and Dolls medley"
      4. Media Report: "Hollywood Babylon II," Japanese condoms, Cardinal Spellman, Michael Musto receives Village Voice column
      COMMERCIAL: Spur Production
      5. 1984 Halloween coverage/ Closing credits
    - [1]--Pride and Progress, Episode No. 7 [2]--The Right Stuff, Episode No. 124 [Air Date: 11/13/1984], November 1984; ID: 231.0606; 155971 (Box 39, Media ID: 231.0606)
    - [1]--Pride and Progress, Episode No. 8 [2]--The Right Stuff, Episode No. 125 [Air Date: 11/20/1984], November 1984; ID: 231.0607; 155972 (Box 39, Media ID: 231.0607)
    - [1]--Pride and Progress, Episode No. 9 [2]--The Right Stuff, Episode No. 126 [Air Date: 11/27/1984], November 1984; ID: 231.0608; 155973 (Box 39, Media ID: 231.0608)
      1. Interview with Nancy Roth, Executive Director, Gay Rights National Lobby, discussing anti-discrimination in immigration policy
      COMMERCIAL: Carnaval in Rio de Janeiro, Islanders' Club
      2. City status granted to West Hollywood, California; city council is formed
      3. Anti-gay Texas Senator Phil [Graham] wins election
      4. Gay Rights bill passed in Houston, Texas, but may be overturned
      COMMERCIAL: "New York Native" with Quentin Crisp
      5. Interview with David Bender, campaigner, discussing the win of Massachusetts' openly gay Senator Gary Studds
      COMMERCIAL: New York Gay Film Festival
      6. National Gay Task Force meeting
      COMMERCIAL: "The Connection," gay and lesbian newspaper
      7. Interview with Pastor Karen Zeigler, Metropolitan Community Church, discusses meeting with National Council of Churches
      8. First census of a gay community, San Francisco
      9. Carol Bellamy, announcement of upcoming appearance
      COMMERCIAL: Arcos Blancos, San Juan, Puerto Rico
      10. Healthline: Conversations with GMHC: Christopher Collins, attorney, discusses the start of Community Health Project
      COMMERCIAL: "Badlands," a NYC gay bar
      11. Sports Report/ closing The Right Stuff:
      1. Media Report/ Current Events
      2. Terry Miller interviews Quentin Crisp, author/ performer
      3. Quentin Crisp interview continued
      COMMERCIAL: National Fund for Human Dignity for disabled gays and lesbians
      4. Preview of upcoming gay motion picture, "Whispers"
      5. Interview with Ron Gould, producer of gay film "Whispers"/ closing credits